What are we getting, I don't want to say we, what are the bulls out there getting wrong about AI?
Because you've made no secret that you don't see any there there.
Yeah, so I think people are conflating a semiconductor rally with an underlying successful
successful business, which doesn't really exist.
Anthropic's current revenue growth, which is deeply questionable,
and the fact that they leaked profitability, manipulated by Elon Musk, of course,
their growth is coming because people cannot measure how much an AI task actually costs.
And a couple months ago, Anthropic started charging their enterprise customers the actual token rates.
What this has led to is suddenly businesses are going,
oh, how much money are we spending?
Uber's, I think it was Uber's COO, Andrew McDonald, said
that they're having trouble justifying the AI spend based on the actual
return that one could actually measure it. So you've got a thing where you can't measure the
costs and you can't measure the return on investment. What do you call that? You call
it a thing without an ROI. Isn't it though safe to say, Ed, like